我们之间所有的通信 所有的未知因素?
All this correspondence? All this not knowing?
你能来我很高兴
I'm just happy you came.
我也是
I'm happy you came.
我必须得承认 我担心了一阵
I have to admit, for a while I was starting to worry
所有的一切最终会成了一个大... 笑话
that this was just gonna turn out to be a big... joke.
- 我也是  - 真的吗?
- Me too. - Really?
是的 没错 我的意思是
Yeah. Sure. I mean,
你和我 我们很能理解这件事情
you and I, we understand this,
但大多数其他人就不一定能够理解
but I don't think a lot of other people would.
吉恩?
Gene?
怎么了?
Yeah?
我感觉... 我准备好了
I think... I think I'm ready now.
好的 丹
OK, Dan. OK.
- 来吧 躺这  - 谢谢
- OK. Here, buddy. - Thanks.
- 好的 - 小心头
- OK. - Watch your head.
躺好了
There you go.
你准备好了吗 丹?
You ready, Dan?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
好的
Ok.
- 你切下来了吗?  - 我搞定了
- Did you get it? - I got it.
保持别动
You hold that.
然后这样就好了
There we go.
好了 完成
Nice. Nice.
闻起来... 还不错
It smells... good.
我也觉得 我... 我没料想到闻起来还不错
I know, right? I wa... I wasn't expecting that.
你呢?
Were you?
我也没想到
No.
它闻起来像...
It smells like...
我之前从来... 没闻过的味道
nothing I've ever... ever smelled before.
- 对吗?  -  同意
- Right? - Yeah, agreed.
- 很奇怪 - 闻起来真香
- It's weird. - It smells incredible.
是的 的确是
Yeah. It really, really does.
真香
Nice.
你感觉怎么样了? 还在流血吗?
How you doin'? How's the bleeding?
暂时没问题
It's under control for now.
太好了
OK, great.
到这边来
Let's just get you over here.
谢谢
Thanks.
然后坐好了
There you go.
好了
Ok.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Well, you're welcome.
不 我意思是 谢谢你...
No, I mean, thank you...
为了我... 和我...
for doing for me... with me...
一起做别人不能理解的事情
What nobody else seems to understand.
我同时也要感谢你
Thank you for the same.
我意思是 我很激动 下次就轮到我了
I mean, I'm excited for this. And for my turn next.
顺便一提 也不怎么疼
It didn't hurt much at all, by the way.
可以开动了吗?
Shall we?
在它变凉之前?
Before it gets cold?
警察! 开门!
This is the police! Open up!
- 天啊 警察? - 什么?
- Jesus Christ. - What?
开门!
Open up!
来了!  正从浴室出来!
Coming! I'm just getting out of the bathroom!
快过来 这边来 快点
OK, come on, come on, come on.
快点
Come on.
呆着别动
OK. Stay in here
不论发生什么不要出来
and don't come out no matter what.
好的
Ok.
别 别 你不能出来
No, no, no, no, no.
- 真好吃!  - 真的吗?
- It's so good! - Really?
- 那是什么声音?  - 没什么! 马上出来!
- What's that? - Nothing! Just a sec!
你有毛病吗?
What the hell is wrong with you?
哇 太好吃了
Oh. So good.
你再不开门
If you don't open this door,
我就要破门而入了
I'm gonna be forced to break it down.
抱歉 来了!
Sorry. Coming!
发生什么了 警官?
How can I help you, Officer?
你为什么花了这么长时间开门?
Why did it take you so long to open this door?
我说了 我在浴室
I told you. I was in the bathroom.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
- 我名字?  - 对 你名字
- M-My name? - Yes, your name.
-吉恩  - 姓什么?
- Gene. - Gene what?
吉恩・歌肯
Gene Gerkin!
丹・本德 今晚和你在一起吗?
Is there a Dan Bender here with you tonight?
我不认识你说的那人
Uh, I don't know anyone by that name.
那这是给谁吃的?
Well, who's all this for?
我和我的朋友
Um, for me. My friend.
让我们来看看这个
Let's see here.
吉尔・本德
Jill Bender.
她上周在她老公丹的电脑上
She found some unusual and cryptic emails
发现了一些不正常的加密邮件
on her husband Dan's computer last week.
她没有透露内容 但是很担心他
She did not divulge the content, but became concerned.
所以一路跟踪到这里
She followed him here
并看到他在十分钟之前
and watched him walk into this room
走进了你的房间
ten minutes ago.
她根据这些邮件里的内容
She called us to check it out,
担心会危害到他的生命
as she had reason to fear his life,
所以叫了我们过来检查
based on his emails.
你现在想告诉我他在哪儿了吗?
You want to tell me where he's at?
我必须得问一句
You know, I have to ask,
你难道不需要搜查证吗?
isn't this something you generally need a warrant for?
我建议你告诉我他在哪
I suggest you tell me where the gentleman is.
我明白你说的
I understand that,
但是我付了房费
it's just I paid for this hotel room
并且我没有做错任何事情
and I'm not doing anything wrong here.
他在这吗?
Is he here?
他藏起来了?
Is he hiding?